Simple text without any formatting
Another simple line of text
Bold text and italic text
Underlined and strikethrough text
Red Green Blue text
Yellow outline magenta outline
Centered positioned text
Bottom left bottom right top left
Small medium large font sizes
Arial Times Courier
Rotated text at 45 degrees
Wide tall small
Moving from left to right
Moving down with timing
Spinning text animation
Growing text
Color transition
Complex multi-effect
3D rotation with colors
Simple fade in and out
Complex fade with timing
Text clipped to rectangle
Animated clipping
Karaoke text
Singing in the rain
Unicode: こんにちは世界！
Mixed: Hello こんにちは 🌍 مرحبا
Emoji: 🎬🎭🎪🎨🎯🎲🎸🎺🎻🎹
Math: ∑∫∂∇∞≠≤≥±∓
This is a very long line of text that should test the performance of parsing and rendering when dealing with substantial amounts of content in a single subtitle event.
Overlapping subtitle 1
Overlapping subtitle 2
Overlapping subtitle 3
Thick border text
Text with shadow
Blur effect text
Strong blur effect
Semi-transparent text
Primary alpha outline alpha
Rotation around center
Double rotation around point
Layer 1 content
Layer 2 content
Layer 3 content
Extreme complexity animation with multiple transforms, fades, and color changes
End of benchmark samples