Scrolling banner across the very top of the frame
Counter-scrolling secondary banner just below
ROTATING TITLE
pulsing scale
colour fade to red over time
growing gaussian blur sample
thickening outline border
perspective X spin approximation
perspective Y spin approximation
fading in and out repeatedly subtitle one
fading in and out repeatedly subtitle two
Karaoke highlight sweep across words
secondary karaoke fill style line here
left vertical sign
right vertical sign
stretching scroll bottom
shearing text via fax over time
shearing text via fay over time
alpha ramp from transparent
two stage primary colour
animated outline colour sample
rising centred caption from the bottom edge
descending centred caption from the top edge
letter spacing animation sweep
tilted diagonal label spinning
wide moving lower-third title bar text
combined blur and border growth
horizontal stretch only sample
vertical stretch only sample
moving and fading mid screen caption