We sing a song to night to geth er
Un der neath the sil ver moon light
Top centred caption that fades in and out
Left aligned note fading on a cycle
Right aligned note fading on a cycle
Colour shifting title text over time
Two stage colour transition line
Fading out gradually via alpha transform
Outline colour animation example line
Directed by Someone Notable
Produced by Another Person Entirely
Music by The Composer And Orchestra
Cinematography by A Camera Operator
Edited by The Person In The Dark Room
Costume Design by The Wardrobe Team
Visual Effects by A Studio Somewhere
Scrolling marquee ticker across the middle band
Lower third descriptive subtitle line here
Speaker name lower left with quick fade
Location label lower right with slow fade
Full line karaoke fill style sweep across
Combined colour shift and fade in
Combined colour shift and fade out
Reverse scrolling secondary ticker line
Mid screen alternating fade caption block
Cho rus line re peat ing now
Annotation bubble left side fading
Annotation bubble right side fading
Rising caption settling into the centre
Half fading persistent watermark style line