Simple dialogue line 1
Bold text with formatting
Italic and underlined text
Red green blue colors
Big small font sizes
Positioned text in center
Moving text across screen
Rotated text at 45 degrees
Scaled text wide and short
Semi-transparent text
Fading in and out
Spinning transformation
Growing animation
Clipped text region
Origin rotation test
Heavy border and shadow
Blurred text effect
Bottom left alignment
Bottom right alignment
Top left alignment
Top right alignment
Y-axis rotation
X-axis rotation
こんにちは世界！Japanese text
Привет мир! Russian text
مرحبا بالعالم Arabic text
你好世界 Chinese text
🌍🚀✨🎭🎪 Emoji test
∑∫∂∇∞≠≤≥±∓ Mathematical symbols
Main Title Style
Subtitle style text
Karaoke timing
Fill karaoke timing
Outline karaoke effect
Wrap style smart wrapping test with long text that should wrap
Border edge blur effect
Custom font family
Letter spacing adjustment
Multi-color test
Multi-alpha test
Inverse clipping test
Delayed movement
Color transition
Alpha transition
Reset then format
Fade in and out
Red border effect
Very long text line that tests the renderer's ability to handle extended content without performance degradation or memory issues during processing